(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
(Episode 16)
- Chief Cha.
- Ms. Joo.
What is Ko Eun Seol doing here?
We're personally acquainted,
so I was just curious what happened.
All right, you can go now.
Okay.
So, what brings you
to my office, Ms. Joo?
She seems like more
than just an acquaintance.
Pardon?
I saw how you defended her
at the awards ceremony.
For someone to step in
during a situation like that,
you two must have been very close.
It's nothing like that.
Good, then.
What do you mean by "good?"
If there's nothing between you two,
you'll have no reason
to protect her.
That's what I meant.
There's no need to bring
a troublemaker into Cheongma.
Right?
I'm sure the CEO
will decide for himself.
Exactly.
Isn't that the liquor
you were saving?
If not on a day like today,
then when?
Would you like a glass, Director?
I'm good.
By the way,
how did you find out about
Ko Eun Seol's criminal record?
Her resume seemed suspicious.
So I asked some
of our old classmates,
and bingo.
I wasn't expecting
anything that big,
but I got total goosebumps
when I heard about it.
It was absolutely thrilling.
From now on,
discuss things like that with me first.
Why? Were you that surprised?
You were lucky
it went your way this time,
but in the future, don't be
so impulsive and blab like that.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
It went my way, so who cares?
Why bother with a plan?
Hey, Ms. Park.
This is Ko Eun Seol.
Do you remember me?
Inmate 2751, Ko Eun Seol?
Of course I remember you.
You made my time in prison
so much easier.
Anyway, what's up?
There's a favor I need to ask you.
A favor? Name it.
I'll do anything you ask.
So, what's the favor?
Can you put me in touch
with a business reporter?
I have something to report, sir.
What is it?
I was monitoring the lies spreading
about the contest online,
and now articles are flooding in.
Really? What is this?
"Discrimination
against ex-convicts,"
"outdated HR practices under fire?"
Who on earth leaked this?
Negative reports are out
from several securities firms,
and the stock price
has dropped by 2.8 percent.
Were you the one behind this?
I'm not sure.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Wasn't it you
who leaked to the press?
How could I do something like that?
I'm not that reckless.
And most importantly,
what power do I have, sir?
I see.
I've given it some thought,
and I think
it'd be meaningful to give...
a young person like you
a second chance.
You can start next week.
Really?
Does that mean I'm officially hired?
Yes.
Thank you. Thank you so much, sir.
You may go.
Right.
(PR Director Joo Mi Ran)
Do you think Ko Eun Seol did it?
Of course.
There's nothing to worry about.
What can some
low-level designer accomplish...
just by getting into Cheongma?
Right.
For now, let's focus on our work.
Look into the board members
of the scholarship foundation.
Everything
from their family relationships...
and medical records
to their personal tastes.
Yes, ma'am.
I just came from seeing the CEO.
You're starting next week?
Yes.
It won't be easy.
Anyway, congratulations.
Okay, then. I'll see you next week.
You think I'm going
to let this slide?
Mom,
it won't be long now.
I'll find the real killer...
and make sure
they pay for their crime.
(Scholarship Foundation
Board Member Profiles)
(Battling liver cancer,
Recent reduction in activities)
Battling liver cancer?
Hey, Eun Seol.
What's up?
Here, take this.
What is it?
Congratulations on the new job.
That wasn't cheap, you know.
Thanks.
You'll be late.
Hurry up and get ready for work.
I'm off, Mom.
All right.
This is Ko Eun Seol.
She's joining the team today.
Everyone, say hello.
Hello, I'm Ko Eun Seol.
I look forward to working
with you all.
Ko Eun Seol?
You're the Ko Eun Seol
who won the grand prize?
Do you two know each other?
We went to high school together,
along with Hae Ra. I mean,
along with Ms. Kang.
Oh, I see.
I'm Assistant Manager Lee Young Ung.
I hope we get along.
Yes, I look forward
to working with you.
Team Leader Kang,
aren't you going to say hello?
(Head of Design Team, Kang Hae Ra)
Team Leader Kang.
I'm Kang Hae Ra,
head of the Design Team.
Satisfied?
All right. Mr. Lee, Ms. Kim,
please help Ms. Ko get up to speed.
Good luck, then.
Thanks.
You can use that desk.
Okay, so the first thing
you should do is...
Ms. Kang.
What should I have
Eun Seol do first?
Ji Soo,
do you still think
we're in high school?
I'm sorry.
What task should I assign to Ms. Ko?
Ms. Ko,
I'm analyzing the trends
for the first half of the year,
so how about lending me a hand?
Assistant Manager Lee!
Why are you pawning your work off
on someone else?
You don't want to work?
Then resign and get out.
No, that's not it. I'm sorry.
Then, Ms. Kang,
what is it that I should be doing?
Are you crazy?
What the heck is this?
Officially, it was a mistake.
Unofficially, it's payback
for what you did.
Hey.
What exactly did I do?
Didn't you spread rumors
in the financial district,
causing Cheongma's stock to tank?
Beats me.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
You're unbelievable, Ko Eun Seol.
Why would you go to such lengths
just to get into Cheongma?
Don't tell me
you're still interested in Seok Jin.
And what if I am?
What?
Stop harassing me
and put me to work,
Ms. Kang.
Put someone like you to work?
Just stay out of the way.
Listen up, everyone.
Ko Eun Seol will be leaving soon,
so act like she's not here.
If I catch any of you
talking to her...
Well, you know what'll happen.
- Yes, ma'am.
Did Ms. Kang and Ko Eun Seol
not get along in high school?
That's an understatement.
Ko Eun Seol is really in for it.
But she's no pushover,
so it'll be interesting to watch.
Ms. Kang spilled coffee on me,
so I have to go change my clothes.
I'll be right back.
(CEO Kang Young Hoon)
Did Ko Eun Seol come in today?
Yes.
What's the market sentiment?
Since we issued a correction
and responded proactively,
it seems the whole thing
is blowing over.
You don't need to worry.
Good.
What do you think, Chief Cha?
What are you referring to, sir?
She spreads fake news
to get what she wants...
and goes after it ruthlessly.
Is that really someone
we should hire?
Are you referring to Ko Eun Seol?
That can't be right.
She's not the type of person
to lie to others for her own gain...
or cause them harm.
Really?
How would you know that?
Oh, right.
Since Ko Eun Seol
was Hae Ra's classmate,
I suppose you'd know her.
Were you two close in school?
I know enough about
the kind of person she is.
I see.
Perhaps she's changed.
After ten years in prison,
I wouldn't be surprised
if her very nature has changed.
In any case,
make sure the people
at that awards ceremony...
keep their mouths shut.
I don't want any more trouble
over this.
I've already had them sign
non-disclosure agreements.
Well, then.
Chief Cha.
Yes?
What are your plans with my Hae Ra?
You're not actually thinking
of marrying her, are you?
With your blessing, sir,
I plan to marry her.
And if I don't give you
my permission?
Then I'll wait until you do.
Do you love her?
You can't answer.
And yet you want to marry her?
Marriage...
I think there's more to it
than just love.
However, I do care for Hae Ra.
Perhaps not as much
as she cares for me.
And...
I also believe there is no one
more suited to be Hae Ra's husband.
Is that honesty or arrogance?
It doesn't matter which it is.
I have no intention
of letting you two get married.
You're dismissed.
Yes, sir.
Unbelievable.
You called for me, Ms. Joo?
It's about Director Han Cheol Soo.
He went to college
with CEO Kang, right?
Yes. He was appointed director
on CEO Kang's recommendation.
According to the file you gave me,
it says he's battling liver cancer.
How serious is it?
It's terminal. I heard he has
less than a year left.
Is that right?
Then we'll need
a replacement director soon.
Do you have something else planned?
Find someone
in the Chairman's circle...
who loves money and prestige.
Yes, ma'am.
(PR Director Joo Mi Ran)
Hello.
I'm Ko Eun Seol,
new to the design team.
I see. How can I help you?
I just have a quick question.
Here, this is for you.
You didn't have to do that.
Still, thanks.
So, what did you want to ask?
I need to request a company car
for a client meeting next week,
but I'm not sure
what the process is.
Just get
your team leader's approval...
and then file the request.
Really?
Then, can I be assigned
any car that I want?
Well, no. What kind of car you get
depends on your rank.
- It depends on my rank?
- Yes.
Since you're a new hire,
you'll be assigned a compact car.
I see.
Then what rank do I need to reach
to get a full-size sedan?
A department head.
Department head?
Yes.
But, why do you ask?
Oh, I was just curious...
Actually, I'm just envious.
See you next time, then.
She left ages ago.
Why isn't she back yet?
What do you think you're doing,
slacking off on your first day?
I had nothing to do,
so I took a tour of the building.
What? You took a tour?
Yes.
Assistant Manager Lee, Ji Soo,
let's grab lunch. My treat.
Really? What are you treating us to?
Anything you want.
Then how about steak?
Enjoy your lunch, Eun Seol.
Yes, you too.
(Employee Search)
Where did everyone go?
Oh, they all went to lunch.
Why didn't you go with them?
I wasn't really hungry.
Anyway, what brings you here?
Since it's your first day, I thought
I'd treat everyone to lunch.
Looks like I was a step too late.
You should still eat,
even if you don't have an appetite.
Want to go grab something with me?
No. It's okay.
I'm really not hungry.
All right, then.
Oh, right.
The CEO suspects that you're the one
who leaked the story.
That's not true, is it?
Why aren't you answering?
Don't tell me you did it.
No,
I'd never do something like that.
Exactly.
You're not that kind of person.
Well, keep up the good work.
Teun Teun,
let's have some watermelon.
Okay, Mom.
Here you go.
Gosh, it's so hot.
I feel like I'm boiling alive.
It's too hot.
Mom, what's that sound?
I don't know.
- Dig in.
- Okay.
Gosh, it's hot. I'm boiling alive.
It's too hot.
My goodness, it's so hot.
Gosh, it's hot.
Ma'am, what are you doing out here?
What do you think?
My room's like a sauna,
so I came out here
to catch a breeze.
- Gosh, it's hot.
- What breeze? Goodness.
The sun is scorching out here.
Ma'am,
you're going to get heatstroke.
What's the worst that can happen?
Me dying?
Why? Are you worried you'll have
to deal with a dead body?
Then let me come in
and share the AC with you.
Why don't you come inside
for a bit then?
You should've said so sooner.
My, it's hot.
It's so cool in here.
Oh, my, that watermelon
looks delicious.
Have some, ma'am.
You're such a sweet boy.
You need to keep respecting
your elders like this, okay?
Yes, ma'am.
By the way,
doesn't your dad live with you?
I don't think I've seen him around.
I don't have a dad.
You don't have a dad?
That's right.
Are you divorced?
Ma'am, can't you just enjoy the AC
and be on your way?
Come on, that's not very neighborly.
You can tell me all about it.
Why did you get a divorce?
I'm not divorced.
If you're not divorced...
Are you a widow?
Or was the father
never in the picture?
Ma'am,
if you keep invading
my privacy like this,
you won't be able to share our AC.
Look who's bragging
over a little air conditioning.
This watermelon is so sweet.
Goodness.
It's so sweet.
She's so petty.
We'll get our own AC, okay?
Grandma, why are you coming
out of there again?
Were you begging
to share their AC again?
Am I a beggar? Why would I beg?
You said she was stingy.
Why do you keep going back?
It's not like they welcome you.
Whether they welcome me or not
is their business.
What am I supposed to do
when I'm about to boil to death?
Gosh, it's so hot.
That lady can probably
survive anything.
Excuse me.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
About what?
Please do something
about your grandmother.
At this rate, she's going to spend
the entire summer at my house.
I looked into getting an AC,
but they're completely booked up
for the rest of the year.
So?
That's just the situation.
So you're not going to do anything
about her coming over?
It's not like I'm forcing her to go.
What?
Then...
I can't believe
how shameless they are!
I'm so furious. Darn it.
Ms. Kang, aren't you heading home?
I will soon. You all go ahead.
See you tomorrow then.
In that case,
I'll be heading out too.
How long are you planning
to stick it out?
It's after hours,
so I can drop
the formalities, right?
Hey.
It's useless no matter what you try.
You know where I've been.
I even survived in there.
Do you really think
this will make me quit?
You're more naive than you look.
Hey, say that again.
All I'm saying is that...
you should pick your fights
more carefully.
Then...
I'll see you tomorrow, Ms. Kang.
Has she lost her darn mind?
Unbelievable!
How's this tea?
It's nice. Why?
This is a special tea sent by
a Cheongma scholarship student...
to say thank you.
Is that right?
It's nice of them to express
their gratitude like this.
Tell me about it.
That's why I'm thinking
of increasing...
the scholarship budget next year.
What? By how much?
About 30 percent?
Honey, no, we can't do that.
What? Why not?
Honey, it's already enough.
With raw material costs soaring,
we have so many other expenses.
And you want to increase
the scholarship budget?
We should be cutting it,
if anything.
Don't you know the company
has to do well first...
for the foundation to be maintained?
That's true, but...
All right.
Gosh, you're too idealistic
for your own good.
Do you think running a business
is that easy?
I said I get it.
What...
I think the Chairman
is a little upset.
I'll just have
to make it up to her tomorrow.
Let's see.
(June 5: 12 suspects
with access to company cars)
What's this?
This lists everyone who had access
to the company car...
used to meet Lee Jung Tae on June 5.
Are you saying that
one of the people here...
is the culprit we're looking for?
Yes.
How did you figure this out?
According to General Affairs,
those cars are only assigned
to department heads.
So after excluding people
dispatched overseas or on leave,
I narrowed it down
to department heads at HQ.
I see.
Eun Seol, this is incredible.
How did you find all this out
in one day?
Then we should start by looking into
what they were doing on June 5.
We'll do that together.
I'll do it by myself.
Why?
I can't put you in danger too,
Attorney Seo.
Eun Seol, come on.
If anything happens to me,
we'll still need you at Cheongma.
Don't you agree?
Then promise me you'll reach out
if you need help.
Of course.
(Cheongma)
What's this?
It's five years' worth...
of competitor product review data
and market research reports.
And?
Sort all this by brand, material,
price range, and sales trends,
and compile everything
into a database.
Sure. Understood.
I need it next week, so finish it
by the end of this week.
Wait, all of this by this week?
What's wrong? Can't you do it?
If you can't, then leave.
No. I'll get it done.
You should've said so
in the first place.
(Cheongma Scholarship Foundation,
Chairman Kim Jung Sun)
Honey.
Let's go to lunch.
Go by yourself.
Are you pouting
because of what I said yesterday?
Come on, don't pout
over something like that.
It's not like you.
Saying it once would've been enough.
Did you have to embarrass me
like that in front of Director Joo?
What? Embarrass you?
Well, you shouldn't have said
something so childish.
Honey.
Forget it.
You need to focus less
on other things...
and start looking
for potential suitors for Hae Ra.
It's time to let go of Seok Jin.
Why? Did something happen
with Seok Jin?
What a joke.
He said he'd marry her
if I gave my permission,
so I asked him if he loves Hae Ra.
He couldn't answer me.
What? Really?
Yes.
He's just trying to marry her
for her background.
That shameless jerk.
Come on, I doubt that.
You're also searching for a suitor
from a good family,
so why blame Seok Jin?
What?
Am I wrong?
How is that the same?
You're unbelievable.
You're buying lunch, right?
Of course. Now, let's go.
- Come on.
- Unbelievable.
- I'll let it go this time.
- Let's go.
All right. Shall we?
Ms. Kang, aren't you going to lunch?
I am.
What should we eat today?
How about that new taco place?
Tacos? Sure, sounds good.
Eun Seol, aren't you having lunch?
You all go ahead.
Okay, then.
(Sales Operations Team)
(September, August, July, June, May)
June...
(June 4-8: Shanghai business trip,
11: Trip report)
Hold on.
How did you and Ko Eun Seol
first meet?
I was Eun Seol's defense lawyer
when she was framed.
I see.
Then can you tell me
what happened back then?
What about it?
I'm curious about the circumstances
of her mother's death,
and how Eun Seol was framed.
Why are you curious about that?
Oh, right. You were
her senior in high school.
Please, tell me. I'm asking you.
No, I'm afraid I can't do that.
As her lawyer, I'm bound
by attorney-client privilege.
- Well, then.
- By any chance,
was Eun Seol the one
who leaked the story about her?
No.
No?
That's right. Eun Seol didn't do it.
How do you know that?
How do you know that it wasn't her?
(A Trap Called Desire)
You should start thinking
about a replacement director.
I knew I could count on you
to look out for me, Director Joo.
I'm going to take
Seok Jin away from you.
Let's get along.
If you can't, at least fake it.
What is it that you want?
A kiss.
I'm warning you.
Stop hanging out with Eun Seol.
There's something
I absolutely need to confirm,
Could you please show it to me?
You two don't seem like
just friends from school.
I hope you don't do anything
to disappoint me.
You're hiding something, aren't you?
Eun Seol, you're nothing like
the Ko Eun Seol I remember.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)